What are you doing there?
I'll ask again.
What do you think you're doing?
That was careless.
What was I even thinking?
I got lost and ended up here.
You got lost? Are you with the mining team?
This is the boss room. Get clear.
Cha Hae-in... The rumors about her
weren't exaggerating.
I didn't notice she was there
until she spoke up.
Was I seeing things?
Didn't he have a weapon a moment ago?
Sorry.
You need to leave this area right away.
If you were to agitate the boss right now,
the entire mining team could be wiped out.
Understood.
Hey, wait a second!
Yes?
He doesn't... stink.
What are you doing?
Are you really a hunter?
Well, yes.
Sung Jinwoo... an E-Rank.
It's not important.
Just be careful on your way back.
This is quite a large dungeon.
Got it.
Is it because of his low rank?
He didn't smell bad.
If anything... he smelled good.
So you got lost and ran into Hunter Cha?
You're a lucky fellow.
The rest of us have to settle for
admiring her from a distance.
She's been patrolling every day during break
time to protect us from the dungeon boss.
She's young, but she's got her act together.
That's why she was by the boss room.
She apparently doesn't like
the way other hunters smell.
The way they... smell?
Some unique condition of hers.
Notice how she's always covering
her nose with that handkerchief?
Right...
But the way she reacted to me...
Maybe I don't have the typical hunter scent?
Come to think of it, the boss of the
red gate said something similar.
Is it because I'm the Player?
Having the system's assistance does
set me apart from everyone else...
But what even is the Player, really?
Good work today.
Thank you.
You helped us finish early.
Can't believe we wrapped up
faster than the collection team.
You're definitely a natural at this job.
I thought you had an excavator
hidden somewhere a few times.
Oh, come on.
I've been doing this for a long time,
and I've never seen anyone
with the knack for it like you.
Mr. Sung, would you like
to come and work for me?
I'll ensure you're paid well!
Oh, no, I appreciate the offer, but...
I only came in because I had some spare time.
I see. That's a real shame.
How about coming in for
just one more day, then?
One more day?
You see, tomorrow's a double-header
for raids—one A-Rank, one C-Rank.
My reassessment is the day after tomorrow.
I was able to earn the money I needed
with today's work, so...
Wait, tomorrow?
There's two Hunters Guild raids tomorrow?
For both A and C Rank?
Yes. That said, there'll be a secondary
strike team showing up tomorrow.
Two teams?
That's one of our strengths.
There aren't many domestic guilds
who can dedicate two teams
to taking down A-Rank gates.
So where should I go tomorrow?
You'll come in, then?
I'll make sure you get paid
double the usual rate, then!
Whoa, I don't know if that's....
Don't you worry about it!
I'd feel guilty otherwise.
Could you look up the details on Sung Jinwoo,
who worked on the mining team today?
Hunter Sung?
You know of him?
Well, Guildmaster Choi asked me
to do the same thing.
The guild master?
Right. But his current details are unavailable.
The Association has a lock on his file,
even though he's not a top-level hunter.
Never seen anything like it.
I see.
The way he was acting in the dungeon...
The fact that Guildmaster Choi
wanted him looked into...
The Association's involvement...
Something's going on here.
I've met so many hunters, but...
He's the first one who smelled good.
Hey, there you are!
Mr. Sung!
Good morning.
Hey, kid. You eat before coming in?
Hello there, Sung.
Jinwoo, try not to get hurt today, okay?
This feeling...
I'd forgotten what it was like.
Let's eat lunch together today.
Yeah, since you're here and all.
Sure.
All right! First is the C-Rank dungeon!
The strike team should be coming
out soon! Everybody get ready!
Impressive again.
The work just gets done faster
with Sung around.
Thanks to him, we can get plenty of rest
before the A-Rank dungeon in the afternoon.
The collection team was surprised, too.
Sure you don't want to come work with us?
I'll pay you five times as much!
Sorry...
Excuse me.
Captain Son Kihoon.
Do you have anyone I can borrow from mining?
Our equipment carrier didn't show.
From us?
Wouldn't someone from the
collection team be better?
They're apparently short-staffed, too.
Since you'll be accompanying the strike team,
you'll also get hazard pay.
Low-rank hunters can't handle carrying
equipment in A-Rank dungeons, sir.
It's not a problem money can solve.
No one at all...?
I'll do it.
Whoa, Mr. Sung!
That's crazy!
There'll be high-ranked beasts in there!
The pay won't be worth the risk!
It's okay.
I'm braver than I look.
It's not a question of courage...
This guy only started yesterday.
He doesn't really understand.
What's his rank?
E-Rank.
So you should find someone—
No, I'd like him to do it.
I'm Son Kihoon, the head of the strike team.
I'm Sung Jinwoo.
The gate's bigger than the one from yesterday.
It has less magic power coming
from it, though.
Don't worry.
We belong to the secondary team,
so they wouldn't leave anything
seriously dangerous to us.
Six A-Ranks...
and three B-Ranks.
There might not be any S-Ranks,
but no other guild would have people
like this in a secondary team.
Let's get going.
The Hunters Guild can field
two teams of this level?
There really is less magic power in the air
than yesterday's dungeon.
But it's weird.
I'm getting the same bad feeling from
when I went through the red gate.
Probably just my imagination.
No need to be nervous.
Kihoon—er, the captain and all
the other hunters here are strong.
As long as you don't run off, you won't
be attacked by a magic beast.
That's good to know.
Once this raid is over,
I'll officially make captain.
I might not be as strong as the
guild master or vice guild master,
but I'm an A-Rank hunter.
I can handle this!
They got ready to fight without any direction.
Here they come!
Dungeon jackals!
Get down!
What are dungeon jackals
doing in an A-Rank dungeon?
Do they not show up usually?
They're C-Rank magic beasts.
They shouldn't be able to survive in here.
Collars?
Look at this. Maybe they belong to someone.
So they were kept alive as hunting dogs?
This explains the bad feeling I had.
High orcs?
Why are they here?!
So powerful!
My taunt skill didn't work?!
It's targeting the back line! Look out!
I'm not going down that easy!
No effect at all?!
How high is its magic resistance?!
It's too strong! I can only keep it
pinned down for a few seconds!
I'll send reinforcements!
You, who my voice awakens...
Collect the head of my foe!
This spell is my secret weapon,
and it costs a ton of mana!
How's that?!
Healer!
We need help over here!
Hang on! I'll be there soon!
There's too many of them!
If we get surrounded, we'll be in real trouble!
Split into groups of three, and spread out!
Even one high orc is a match for
A-Rank hunters... and there's so many.
The B-Ranks don't stand a chance!
Come on, people, stay with me!
Next!
Don't move! I'll heal you right away!
What... just happened?
What is this?
They're suddenly moving slower.
Now!
Push them all the way back!
Hate to butt in as an outsider,
but I can't just let them die.
I'll weaken the enemies
without anyone noticing.
You stay out of this.
Is anyone seriously injured?!
Looks okay over here.
It's a miracle no one was hurt.
Did you notice anything weird during combat?
The one I was fighting started
moving sluggishly all of a sudden.
Was that you, Gina?
I couldn't do that if I wanted to.
I've only got attack magic and
a little bit of telekinesis magic.
And the other mages are all firepower-focused.
We don't have any stealth types,
so none of us should be capable of that.
But however it happened, we still won.
Good point. Let's chalk it up to good luck.
That equipment carrier must think we're a joke.
All these magic casters, and he really believed
no one would notice him using Stealth?
On the other hand,
he did help us out of a tight spot.
I'm sure he has his reasons,
so I'll pretend I didn't see anything.
Captain Son, should we keep going?
This is too dangerous for our strike team.
We'd need at least two more healers
and another three mages.
I know this isn't what you wanted
for your first time as captain,
but I really think we should withdraw.
I get why he wouldn't want to give up.
He obviously wants to clear this dungeon.
But if he's reasonable...
Then let's pull out for now.
I was worried you'd wanna
keep going, to be honest.
I'm not that stupid.
Wh-What the...
It's a barrier. And a powerful one, at that.
It wasn't there when we came this way.
Can you dispel it?
I think so, with enough time.
If there's something in the dungeon
capable of this kind of magic...
then turning back was the right call.
We can't possibly clear this place.
Where is this magic power coming from?!
No way...
Was that the dungeon boss?
Help me out here! We have to hurry!
Got it!
Right!
Enough magic power that even
B-Rank hunters can detect it...
Then why couldn't anyone
sense it from the outside?
A curse?! It must be a trap!
Semi! We need holy magic!
What's wrong?! Why aren't you—
Kihoon... I see at least fifty of them.
Kihoon!
Stay back!
If we fight, we die.
Humans.
I am called Kargalgan.
I would like to meet with you.
Kargalgan, are you the one
who blocked off our exit?
That is right.
I am a proud orcish master of curses.
Is there anyone more powerful
than you in this cave?
Do you think any exist who could surpass me?
Now choose. Will you be killed
by my soldiers or come to me?
We'll meet with you.
Hunter Sung.
Yes?
We're going to attack
as soon as the boss appears.
However that turns out,
he likely won't be able to maintain
the barrier while dealing with us.
That'll be your chance to leave the dungeon
and contact the main strike team.
Don't tell me you plan to die here.
Our objective isn't
to leave this dungeon alive,
but to make sure the gate closes.
I have a request, too.
It's not long, but this is my will.
Please take it to my family.
This is what we're trained to do,
but you have no such duty.
Please try and get out of here alive.
This sense of despair...
It reminds me of the double dungeon.
Back then, the others abandoned me.
But these people...
I'll hold onto it.
But hopefully that won't be necessary.
I don't see him. Did he quit mining work?
Hunter Cha?
What brings you by? Aren't you off today?
Um, is that man, Sung Jinwoo, around today?
Oh, Sung's actually helping out
as a carrier today.
Then...
He's inside of the gate?
I bid you welcome, human worms.